Okay, I got to ask you about the opening
line of this song.
[music and singing]
>> 1952.
>> Can I give you my breakdown? You can
tell me if it's right or or wrong.
Couldn't stop my drive. Obviously, your
ambition. You're referencing a literal
car drive in this metaphor. 1955 was the
year of the Montgomery boycott,
>> tying in this idea of stop my drive.
They refused to ride buses. Y
>> the 85 is the interstate that connects
Atlanta to Montgomery. So connecting
your home
>> around the same time too.
>> 52 Dodge the fastest Dodge from 1952
only goes like 85 or 90. So essentially
the play is like even if the buses were
down highway wasn't built yet. Car
didn't go that fast. You still can't
drop stop my drive
>> 100%. It it literally started with the
initial line. You couldn't even stop my
drive if it was in 1955. That's where
the ideas start coming from. I looked up
when the first Dodge Dodge rhymes with
five a little bit. Try to just make it
all correlate to like you not being able
to stop my intentions, my drive, my
focus.